This is like the most stressful thing I've ever been through.
Where are you staying?
I'm staying at the campgrounds.
Oh, wow, that must be hard.
Where are you staying at?
This is actually staying in this like house.
I was like 85 bedroom.
Like the roof opens and held out of the roof.
It takes you from the roof and it takes you to the festival.
I'm sure the campgrounds are like the experience.
Are you worried about the crowns at all?
Oh my God, girl, I haven't artist passed.
I'm not worried about that at all.
Do you have a bath?
Oh no, I just got general admission.
Oh my, I mean, that will be so fun.
So what party are you going to?
Oh, isn't Coachella the party?
No, so my style is called like eight outfits.
I hated like three of them.
So now I've got to go choose like four more.
So just like, I do.
I'm like stress.